

Novan Noviansyah Pratama

Hi, I am a Mobile developer using Flutter, I have been involved in Flutter for almost two years. In addition, I have also learned other languages such as HTML, CSS and Javascript, PHP (Laravel Framework) besides that, I also teach at the Garut Institute of Technology campus as a Lab assistant for the Basics of Programming, Algorithms and Data Structures, Computer Networks, and Mobile Programming courses.





Work Experience

Mobile App Developer ⋅ Digitalkeun Creative

Garut, West Java, Indonesia

Februari 2023 - Present

IT Staff · PT. Janari Global Nusantara

Bandung Barat, West Java, Indonesia Internship as an IT staff in an agency company.

Oktober 2022 - Januari 2023

Peer Tutor ⋅ Study Group MSIB Dicoding Indonesia X Kampus Merdeka Batch 3

Online

Guide participants to complete class submission

Oktober 2022 - Januari 2023

Computer Lab Assistant - Pemrograman Mobile · Institut Teknologi Garut

Garut, West Java, Indonesia

Teaching Android mobile programming with Dart programming language using Flutter framework.

Februari 2023 - Present

Computer Lab Assistant - Jaringan Komputer · Institut Teknologi Garut

Garut, West Java, Indonesia

Teaching about computer network courses using Cisco Packet Tracer and Mikrotik.

Oktober 2022 - Januari 2023

Computer Lab Assistant - Dasar-dasar Pemrograman · Institut Teknologi Garut

Garut, West Java, Indonesia

Teaching basic programming using C, C++, Python, and Pascal programming languages.

Februari 2022 - Juni 2022

Computer Lab Assistant - Algoritma & Struktur Data · Institut Teknologi Garut

Garut, West Java, Indonesia

Teaching about algorithms and data structure using C, Python, and Pascal programming languages.

September 2021 - Januari 2022

Awards

Distinction (Certified Independent Study) • Dicoding X Kampus Merdeka



Garut, West Java, Indonesia

Distinction Graduated Dicoding MSIB batch 3 Multi-platform and Back-End Development

Organizational

2022 - 2023

Head of Technology Subdivision

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika ITG (HIMATIF ITG)

2019 - 2022

IT Division Member

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika ITG (HIMATIF ITG)

2020 - 2021

Member of Training Division

Komunitas Teknologi dan Informasi ITG (KOMTIK ITG)

Education



Institut Teknologi Garut

Bachelor degree Computer Science

2019 - Present



Dicoding Academy

Studi Independen Bersertifikat Batch 3 -Pengembangan Multi-platform dan Back-End

Agustus 2022 - Januari 2023

Skills

- Communication
- Programming
- Team Management

Language

- Indonesia Native
- English Intermediate